[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "You really can't wait, aren't you?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "You've never been ashamed about anything you've ever done?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I don't -- well, let's go private.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "You mean publicly or privately?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, because I was young and dumb.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Don't flatter me, Whoopi.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "But if you are 40 -- are you about that age?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I just turned 46, but I'll take the first guess.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "May I ask?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Well, I think I must, you know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Do you ever fear death yourself?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Well, I don't like it.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "You are afraid of flying, aren't you?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Was there something that sparked it?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Yes, we saw it.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "You saw it?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, because what they discovered later on is that the people on the plane were aware that they were in some danger, but I think the person who was in the smaller plane had had a heart attack.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Why is it so hard?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "I had a course from the folks at virgin.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "You had a course, didn't you?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Do you have other things that you're worried about?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, I don't like anything that has a weird consistency.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What foods?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I don't understand the point.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Cream corn?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "No, I'm not allergic.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "You're allergic to cream corn?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "You're allergic to milk?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "You can't drink milk and you can't eat cream corn?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Because that's what it's called.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I'm not and I want to be clear, I love corn.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Why do you hate a cream corn?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Please, no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "What, spinach?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I hate spinach.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Again, I appreciate the people who grow it and people --", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "You hate spinach?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "What are we left with?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "No, no, no, I mean potato chips from the bag.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "You just live off fries?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I do eat some meat.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Can you eat meat?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "You're really quite weird, aren't you?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Cream corn is going to kill you.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Isn't it great?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Do you think you were in love with all your husbands?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Any of them?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "But it's the truth.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "It's an amazing thing to say, isn't it?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "You won't -- you have church weddings?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Because I wanted to feel normal.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Why did you do it if you weren't in love with them?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "How my times have you been in love?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "A man.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Who with?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "You could chuck a name.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Can I chuck a name in?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Is that the man I'm talking about?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Would we know who the person is?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Is this a recent thing?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "You wish you'd married that person?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Because what I know now is I don't want to live with -- I don't want to live with anyone.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "OLDBERG: I don't know if I did.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Didn't you like being in love?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think that guy knows he's the only man you've ever loved?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Yes, we talk all the time.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "You still talk to him?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Are you -- are you on the dating scene?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Could you imagine?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Do you get lonely?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not surprised by it because, you know, very few presidents can go on and make the change they want to make.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Are you disappointed that President Obama, who I know you're a massive fan of and supported, hasn't really done that much for gay marriage?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, listen, we didn't tip over the edge, in spite of the fact that, you know, everybody is saying, oh, he hasn't done anything.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Do you think we're getting there perhaps?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Going to take a little break now you're nicely fired up.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "You were raised well by intelligent people for the most part, both of us, and that we know how to say to someone, would this bother you if I did that?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Do you actually -- are you friends with the other co- stars of \"The View\"?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Or are they co-workers that you have to get on with?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Not with them.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Often you looked like you haven't got the patience when you're out there with them?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Don't you find Charlie Sheen's thing fascinating?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Old torpedo winning duh thing?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "You had a problem with drugs, didn't you?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "No, you know what, these are such personal issues.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Whatever you want to do?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Isn't it true that when you won your Oscar, you were actually high as a kite?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "No, God no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Have you ever?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I still smoke cigarettes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You've become really quite squeaky clean, haven't you?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "You've gone after, yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "That I've gone after?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "OLDBERG: I say that's (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "What do you want to say?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Is that ridiculous?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I didn't mean in a bad way.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Am I done?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "No, no, no, I never did.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Did you ever think you'd be on TV every day giving opinion?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "It makes me really, really angry.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "When you hear Donald Trump go after Barack Obama for where he was born, what do you think about it?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Yes, they do.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think a lot of people will believe it anyway?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's not just the politics, you know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Is that the danger of that kind of politics?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "How do you think you would have fared as a young celebrity when you first hit the big-time if the Internet had been around?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I think you'd be surprised.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Well, oh, yes?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Well, you know, if a politician is behaving in your view wrongly or if a right-wing cable host, someone like a Bill O'Reilly or Glenn Beck, whack, whack, whack.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Who have I slapped around?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "You're not defending him?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Because Michael Phelps is an Olympian athlete.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I think that drunks say whatever comes into their head.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Or do you think that the drink loosens tongues, perhaps?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Do you ever get drunk?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Yes, once.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Once?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Once in my life, and I was in public.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "You've been drunk once in your life?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "In New Orleans.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Where was it?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Very drunk.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "How drunk were you?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "He's not smoking weed out in the street.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "You don't think he has any responsibility as a role model?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "Yes, man.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "People -- famous people should consider themselves whatever they want to consider themselves.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "So, no famous people should ever consider themselves to be role models?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "If you're a celebrity, and a few friends of yours have done this, if they sell their wedding for $1 million, are they entitled to privacy?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "Well, I wanted to say for those of you out there who disagree with me in terms of being a role model, save your e-mails.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "What did you want to say?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Yes, as far as I know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "Are you going to be there for two more years?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "Do you love it so much you want to carry on, or is there a natural shelf life to this thing?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "I could do that.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "For the next 20 years you'd do that?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "I'm not telling you.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "You should have asked me.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "You can't take a camel to an oasis and then you say, you can't have a drink.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 799, "question": "A camel to -- OK, can we just talk about that, a camel to the oasis?", "qSentId": 798}, {"answer": "Oh, you know, I've got musicals opening.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "ORGAN: What's on the horizon for you?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "That's about white supremacists?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "Is America more racist or less racist than, say, 20 years ago from your experience?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Because it just feels like questions to me.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "In Donald Trump's defense, I know him quite well, I don't think he's a racist at all.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 837, "question": "When you question this president, the first president we've ever had of color and you're not sure where he was born and it continues, is that about -- what is that about, really?", "qSentId": 836}, {"answer": "I suspect it's about votes, because his poll ratings, the more he hammers this point -- it's probably an anti-Obama vote catching mechanism.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "Or Bill Clinton?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "I just assume it's going to be good times with the family, people that you didn't get to meet because they were gone.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "Ever thought what heaven might be like when you get up there?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "Do you believe in an after life?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Do you pray a lot?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "Probably?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "I suppose --", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "Well, no, I mean, it depends -- how do you describe praying?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "Not necessarily going to church, but talking to an entity that is not physically there and asking for help.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 873, "question": "Going to church and stuff?", "qSentId": 872}, {"answer": "OLDBERG: No, no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Do you do that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "I could use some backup.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "What's your idea of prayer?", "qSentId": 877}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "Do you go to any church?", "qSentId": 880}, {"answer": "Very rarely.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 884, "question": "At all?", "qSentId": 883}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 913, "question": "And it can't be the birth of my kid?", "qSentId": 912}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 915, "question": "Or my grand kids?", "qSentId": 914}, {"answer": "That was very, very nice.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 924, "question": "How about winning an Oscar?", "qSentId": 923}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 942, "question": "Do you know who Moms Mabley was?", "qSentId": 941}, {"answer": "OLDBERG: April 20th.", "docId": "110416pmt", "aSentId": 961, "question": "When does it open?", "qSentId": 960}]